tremeritus.com 2012-06-30

# Privacy Policy « TR EMERITUS

**Our Commitment to Privacy**

Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal data you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the TR Emeritus (TRE) Web site..

Our Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. You should check our Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are aware of our latest policies.  
**  
What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit the TRE Web site, we may collect two types of information from you: personal data you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and the TRE Web site user information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse the TRE Web site.

**Cookies**

The TRE Web site utilises Web server logs and will use a standard technology called “cookies” to recognize you and your access privileges on the TRE Web site as well as to collect information about how the TRE Web site is used. Information gathered by using cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at the TRE Web site, and the web sites you visited immediately before and after the TRE Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

**IP Addresses**

Like all other servers in the world, we log IP addresses or the location of your computer on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We do not use IP address logs to track your session or your behaviour on the TRE Web site.

More information at [How ‘exposed’ are you when you visit TR Emeritus](http://www.tremeritus.com/2012/02/26/how-exposed-are-you-when-you-visit-tr-emeritus/ "Permanent Link to How ‘exposed’ are you when you visit TR Emeritus")

.

Updated 25th February 2012
